[
  {
    "question": "1.Which company developed android?",
    "answer1": "Apple",
    "answer2": "Google",
    "answer3": "Android Inc.",
    "answer4": "Nokia",
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "2. Which company bought android?",
    "answer1": "Apple",
    "answer2": "No Company",
    "answer3": "Nokia",
    "answer4": "Google",
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "3. Web browser available in android is based on",
    "answer1": "Chrome",
    "answer2": "Firefox",
    "answer3": "Open-source Webkit",
    "answer4": "Opera",
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "4. Android is based on which kernel?",
    "answer1": "Linux Kernel",
    "answer2": "Windows Kernel",
    "answer3": "MAC Kernel",
    "answer4": "Hybrid Kernel",
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "5. Android is based on which language",
    "answer1": "C",
    "answer2": "C++",
    "answer3": "Kotlin",
    "answer4": "C#",
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "6.  If you want to increase the whitespace between widgets, you will need to use the ____________ property",
    "answer1": "Android:padding",
    "answer2": "Android:digits",
    "answer3": "Android:capitalize",
    "answer4": "Android:autoText",
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "7. Which of the following Dialog boxes are supported by Android? 1) AlertDialog 2) ProgressDialog 3) DatePickerDialog 4) TimePickerDialog",
    "answer1": "1 and 2",
    "answer2": "3 and 4",
    "answer3": "all of the above",
    "answer4": "none of the above",
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "8. Using a content provider, which of the following operations are able to perform? 1) create 2) read 3) update 4) delete",
    "answer1": "1,2,3",
    "answer2": "2,3,4",
    "answer3": "all of the above",
    "answer4": "none of the above",
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "9. Which of the following are different storage methods available in Android? 1) Shared Preferences 2) Internal Storage 3) External Storage 4) SQLite Databases 5) Network Connection 6)Intermediate storage",
    "answer1": "1,2,3,4,6",
    "answer2": "2,3,4,5,6",
    "answer3": "1,2,3,4,5",
    "answer4": "all",
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "10. In ___________, sender specifies type of receiver.",
    "answer1": "implicit intent",
    "answer2": "explicit intent",
    "answer3": "both",
    "answer4": "none",
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "11. Which of the following(s) is/are component of APK file?",
    "answer1": "Resources",
    "answer2": "Delvik Executable",
    "answer3": "both",
    "answer4": "none",
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "12. Which of the following donâ€™t have any UI component and run as a background process?",
    "answer1": "Services",
    "answer2": "simulator",
    "answer3": "Emulator",
    "answer4": "none",
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "13. What are the layouts available in android?",
    "answer1": "LinearLayout",
    "answer2": "FrameLayout",
    "answer3": "TableLayout",
    "answer4": "all",
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "14. How to store heavy structured data in android?",
    "answer1": "SharedPreferences",
    "answer2": "Cursor",
    "answer3": "SQLite database",
    "answer4": "Not possible",
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "15. Is it mandatory to call onCreate() and onStart() in android?",
    "answer1": "No, we can write the program without writing onCreate() and onStart()",
    "answer2": "Yes, we should call onCreate() and onStart() to write the program",
    "answer3": "At least we need to call onCreate() once",
    "answer4": "none",
    "correctAnswer": 2
  }
]